speakeasy.net 2016-03-19

# 

                                 MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC Privacy Policy Statement
This is the website of MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC
Contact us
By mail
6800 Koll Center Parkway, Suite 200
Pleasanton, California 94566
By e-mail
privacyofficer@megapath.com
By telephone
1-877-MEGAPATH
By facsimile
1-925-201-2550
Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy discloses how MegaPath Cloud
Company, LLC (“MegaPath”) collects, protects, uses and shares personal information gathered
about you. All Personal Information is collected in a fair and non-intrusive manner, with your
voluntary consent. Personal Information is not accessible to anyone outside the specific function
for which it is collected. MegaPath respects the privacy of our customers, our employees and
other visitors to our websites who may choose to provide personal information. We recognize the
need for appropriate protections and management of personal information that you provide to us.
This Privacy Policy will help you to understand what types of information we may collect, how that
information may be used, and with whom the information may be shared.
This Privacy Policy explains MegaPath’s practices regarding the information collected online from
users of the MegaPath website located at www.megapath.com.
In an effort to comply with the law, and our commitment to protect your personal information, we
provide the following, which discloses our policies.
What type of information do we collect?
Personal Information is defined as any information concerning the personal or material
circumstances of an identified or identifiable individual. An identifiable person is one who can be
identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to a Social Security Number and/or Identification
Number (hereinafter “SSN/I.N”) or to one or more factors specific to his physical, physiological,
mental, economic, cultural or social identity.
Personal Information shall include but is not limited to: name, home address, home telephone
number, email address, Social Security Number and/or Identification Number, financial
information and employment related information such as may be found on resumes, applications,
background verification information, or in employment references.
MegaPath does not collect SSN/I.N. information or date of birth information from our website or
from our customers. MegaPath does collect SSN/I.N. and date of birth information from job
applicants and employees. MegaPath takes measures to maintain the confidentiality of such
information from unlawful disclosure, and to limit access to the information. MegaPath will not
make your SSN/I.N or date of birth available to the general public, print it on any card, require you
to provide your it to access any products or services, transmit this information over the Internet
Version 04-23-15                                                                           Page 1 of 5

                                MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC Privacy Policy Statement
unless the connection is secure or your the information has been encrypted, or require the
transmittal of this information to access our Website. MegaPath is PCI-DSS compliant and will
use PCI standards in protecting the information described in this paragraph.
Non-personal information is information that is already a matter of public record or knowledge.
Business contact information is considered non-personal information and no subjected to special
protection and it can be routinely shared with anyone inside or outside of the business. Business
contact information shall include but is not limited to: business name, business address,
business telephone number, and is not considered personal information in certain jurisdictions.
Cookies – Internet Users
In addition to Personal Information, we use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain
web pages to help analyze our web page flow and measure promotional effectiveness. Cookies
are pieces of information a website sends to an individual’s hard drive while they are viewing the
website. Cookies allow the website to remember important information that will make your visit to
the site more useful. We use cookies to help improve your future visits. If you do not wish to
receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent,
or if you wish to turn off all cookies, use the options on your browser to assist you. The “Help”
option on your browser may assist you in changing your cookie preferences. Please note that by
turning cookies off, you will not have access to many features available on our website.
Children and Data Collection
MegaPath adheres to the federal privacy protection standards as stated in the Children’s Online
Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We care about the safety of children. We will not knowingly
allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children under 13
years of age are required to obtain the express permission of a parent or guardian before
submitting any Personal Information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail address, and
phone number) over the Internet. If a child has provided us with personally-identifiable
information without the consent of a parent or guardian, the parent or guardian of that child
should contact the Privacy Officer immediately at privacyofficer@megapath.com. We will use
reasonable efforts to promptly delete the child’s information from our servers.
A Special Note about Children who reside in the State of Maine, USA
MegaPath complies with the Maine state law titled “An Act to Prevent Predatory Marketing
Practices against Minors”. The law applies to the collection and use of personal information for
marketing purposes of children who are under the age of 18. The www.megapath.com website
which is developed and serviced by MegaPath Inc is not intended to solicit information of any kind
from children under 18 years of age. It is possible that due to fraud or deception by others, we
may unknowingly receive information pertaining to children under 18 years of age. If this is the
case, the parent or guardian of the minor must notify the Privacy Officer immediately at
privacyofficer@megapath.com.
Our Use of Your Personal Information
We use your Personal Information to facilitate the services you request. We have tailored our
Privacy Policy to adequately advise of the use of your Personal Information.
Collection and Use of Employee Personal Information
MegaPath also collects Personal Information from its employees and applicants (human resource
data) in connection with administration of its Human Resources programs and functions although
not through MegaPath’s website. These programs and functions include, but are not limited to:
job applications and hiring programs, compensation and benefit programs, performance
appraisals, training, access to MegaPath facilities and computer networks, employee profiles,
internal intranet employee directories, Human Resource recordkeeping and other employment
related purposes.
Version 04-23-15                                                                         Page 2 of 5

                               MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC Privacy Policy Statement
It is the policy of MegaPath to keep all past and present employee information private from
disclosure to third parties. There are certain business related exceptions and they are:
     1. To comply with county, state or federal agency requests;
     2. Inquiries from third parties with a signed authorization from the employee to release the
         information, except in situations where limited verbal verifications are acceptable (see
         below);
     3. Third parties with which MegaPath has contractual agreements to assist in administration
         of company sponsored benefits.
Verifications of Employment
Prospective employers, financial institutions, and residential property managers routinely contact
MegaPath requesting information on a former or current employee’s work history and salary. All
such requests of this type shall be referred to and completed on a confidential basis by the
Human Resources Department or Payroll Department.
For written verification of employment requests, information will be provided on the form only
when it is accompanied by an employee’s signed authorization to release information. The form
will be returned directly to the requesting party and filed as part of the Human Resources or
Payroll Department’s confidential records.
Medical Information
MegaPath is compliant with federal HIPAA regulations and only utilizes information related to the
company sponsored healthcare plan on a “need to know” basis for administration of the
healthcare plan.
Collection and Use of Customer Information
MegaPath will not collect customer Personal Information, unless the customer contacts
MegaPath directly. Failure to provide necessary information may prevent MegaPath from fully
addressing any customer concerns.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with
information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such
mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above. Please provide us with
your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from our mailing list.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from
us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish
to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the above address.
Please provide us with your name and phone number and we will be sure your name is removed
from our telemarketing list.
A customer requesting services from MegaPath through the www.megapath.com website will be
asked to provide Personal Information. The Personal Information collected may include, but will
not be limited to: name, e-mail address, telephone number, and credit card information.
MegaPath will not collect Personal Information, unless you contact MegaPath directly. In the
future, MegaPath may use this information to contact you regarding products or promotions, as
well as other products and services, which may be of interest to you. If you do provide us with
Personal Information we may use the information to contact you, via e-mail, regular mail,
telephone or other means, to provide you with information that you requested about specific
products or services, provide additional future information about products or services that may be
of interest to you, and to learn about and develop products and services. If you do not want this
information disclosed you may “opt out” of future contacts at any time by un-subscribing from our
Version 04-23-15                                                                         Page 3 of 5

                                MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC Privacy Policy Statement
database or contacting the Privacy Officer, in writing, as described below in the section titled
“Contact Information”.
Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which
it was originally collected by calling us at the number provided above.
Upon request, we provide site visitors and customers with access to all information [including
proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Requests for this information should be sent
to the above e-mail address. Any corrections to this information should also be sent to the above
e-mail address.
Sharing of Personal Information
We may share Personal Information with our service providers, consultants and affiliates for our
internal business purposes. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, MegaPath will not share
Personal Information with a third party, unless a customer requests, consents to such disclosure,
or disclosure is required or authorized by law. MegaPath reserves the right to disclose Personal
Information to a third party if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order legally
requires or authorizes us to do so. Please see our Subpoena Policy for additional information.
MegaPath also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer Personal Information to a third party
in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other
type of acquisition, disposal, or financing of all or any portion of MegaPath or of any of the
business or assets or shares of MegaPath or a division thereof in order for a customer to continue
to receive the same products and services from the third party.
Personal Information may be provided to a courier or freight forwarder to fulfill an order, which
may have been requested from us.
Service providers are prohibited from using Personal Information for any purpose other than to
provide assistance to MegaPath. Service Providers are required to protect Personal Information
disclosed by us and to comply with the general privacy principles described in this Privacy Policy.
Security
We endeavor to protect your Personal Information using physical, electronic or procedural
security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our control. These measures
include safeguards to protect Personal Information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized
access, disclosure, copying, use and modification. MegaPath is PCI-DSS compliant and will use
PCI standards in protecting the information described in this paragraph
We safeguard your Personal Information on the Internet by using industry-standard practices.
Although “guaranteed security” does not exist either on or off the Internet, we make commercially
reasonable efforts to make the collection and security of such information consistent with our
Privacy Policy and all applicable laws and regulations. We maintain physical, electronic and
procedural safeguards as appropriate to safeguard your Personal Information.
Currently, our website utilizes a variety of different security measures designed to protect
Personal Information by users both inside and outside MegaPath, including the use of encryption
mechanisms (e.g., Secure Socket Layers or SSLs), password protection, and other security
measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. This
helps maintain the confidentiality, privacy, and integrity of your transactions, and helps to protect
your confidential information – such as credit card numbers, online forms and financial data, from
loss, misuse, interception and hacking.
Storage, Retention and Accuracy of Personal Information
Version 04-23-15                                                                          Page 4 of 5

                                 MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC Privacy Policy Statement
MegaPath insures that Personal Information is safeguarded against loss, access, use,
modification, disclosure or other misuse. All reasonable steps are taken to prevent unauthorized
use or disclosure of your Personal Information.
MegaPath will retain your Personal Information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the
purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws and your consent to such
purpose remains valid after termination of our relationship with you.
We take all reasonable steps to insure that your Personal Information is accurate, up-to-date,
complete, relevant and not misleading.
Contact Information
You may contact the Privacy Officer to access, correct or delete your Personal Information. If
necessary, the Privacy Officer will contact another individual to assist in completing your
requested task.
If you have any questions or complaints, please contact the Privacy Officer. The Privacy Officer
can     be     reached        by     telephone      at:    1-877-MEGAPATH;        by    email     at:
privacyofficer@megapath.com; or by mail at MegaPath Cloud Company, LLC, 6800 Koll
Center Parkway, Suite 200, Pleasanton, CA, 94566, USA. We will address your concern and
attempt to resolve any problem.
Links to Non-MegaPath Web Sites and Third Parties
Please note that www.megapath.com websites may contain links to other websites for your
convenience and information. MegaPath does not control those sites or their privacy practices,
which may differ from www.megapath.com. MegaPath’s privacy policy cannot and does not
apply to external websites. We do not endorse or make any representations about third party
websites. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by the
MegaPath privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company or
website before submitting your Personal Information. Some third parties may choose to share
their personal data with MegaPath; that sharing is governed by that third party company’s privacy
policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
MegaPath will update this Privacy Policy occasionally. When MegaPath posts changes to this
Privacy Policy, we will also revise the “Last Updated” date below on MegaPath’s Privacy Policy.
MegaPath encourages you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be informed of how
MegaPath is protecting your information and to be aware of any changes to the Privacy Policy.
Your continued use of the site after the posting of any amended Privacy Policy shall constitute
your agreement to be bound by any such changes. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into any
Terms and Conditions governing the various web sites and any programs or services operated or
managed b or on behalf of MegaPath. Any changes to this Privacy Policy are effective
immediately after being posted by MegaPath.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the
above addresses or phone number, or The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at
mgoldberger@the-dma.org.
Last Updated: 04/23/2015
Version 04-23-15                                                                          Page 5 of 5
